http://www.sciencetech-inc.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode

Sciencetech Inc
Search:
Search
Categories
ProductsLight SourcesLight Sources OverviewXenon Arc Lamp Light SourcesQTH Light SourceTunable Light SourcesPower SupplyInfrared Light SourcesCalibration Light SourcesLight Source AccessoriesSolar Simulation and PV Testing EquipmentSteady State Solar SimulatorsFlash Solar SimulatorsModular IV Test EquipmentQuantum Efficiency Measurement SystemFar Infrared Systems (THz)Far Infrared Systems OverviewFar Infrared SpectrometersDetectorsAccessoriesSample ChambersFar Infrared Light SourcesModular SpectrometersMonochromator and SpectrographsSample ChambersData Acquisition EquipmentOpto-Mechanical SoftwareDetectorsSingle Channel DetectorsLine and Area DetectorsElectrochemical WorkstationsOptical ComponentsFiltersGratingsFilters for Solar SimulationReflectorsCustom SolutionsCustom CapabilitiesSuccess StoriesApplicationsSpectroscopyFluorescence SpectroscopyRaman SpectroscopySpectroradiometer for Detector CharacterizationFar Infrared SpectroscopySpectrophotometryRadiometryPhotocatalysisPhotovoltaics and Materials TestingPhoton CountingLIBSContact UsSales ContactRepresentativesSupport ContactResources
ProductsLight SourcesLight Sources OverviewXenon Arc Lamp Light SourcesQTH Light SourceTunable Light SourcesPower SupplyInfrared Light SourcesCalibration Light SourcesLight Source AccessoriesSolar Simulation and PV Testing EquipmentSteady State Solar SimulatorsFlash Solar SimulatorsModular IV Test EquipmentQuantum Efficiency Measurement SystemFar Infrared Systems (THz)Far Infrared Systems OverviewFar Infrared SpectrometersDetectorsAccessoriesSample ChambersFar Infrared Light SourcesModular SpectrometersMonochromator and SpectrographsSample ChambersData Acquisition EquipmentOpto-Mechanical SoftwareDetectorsSingle Channel DetectorsLine and Area DetectorsElectrochemical WorkstationsOptical ComponentsFiltersGratingsFilters for Solar SimulationReflectorsCustom SolutionsCustom CapabilitiesSuccess StoriesApplicationsSpectroscopyFluorescence SpectroscopyRaman SpectroscopySpectroradiometer for Detector CharacterizationFar Infrared SpectroscopySpectrophotometryRadiometryPhotocatalysisPhotovoltaics and Materials TestingPhoton CountingLIBSContact UsSales ContactRepresentativesSupport ContactResources
Home
>
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy / Information Submitted and Collected / Use of Information
It's important to Sciencetech Inc to help our customers and visitors to our web site retain their privacy when they take advantage of all the Internet has to offer.
For more than 28 years, Sciencetech has been an established manufacturer and market-leading supplier of test, measurement and inspection equipment. Our success is based upon being able to provide superior products at a fair price and in building long-term trust-based relationships with our customers. Sciencetech's policies reflect these ideals to the extent that it's simply the way we do business. We've been protecting sensitive customer information for many more years than the Internet has been around. And while the Internet makes it easier to collect some of this information, it in no way diminishes our ability to protect it.
Acceptance of Terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of the terms of Sciencetech's Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site and exit the Site immediately. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean that you accept those changes.
Information Submitted and Collected; Use of Information
Personal Information
When you use Sciencetech-inc.com (the "Site"), we will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you, such as your name, title, company affiliation, address, telephone numbers, and email address. Generally this information is requested when you make an online purchase, request literature, request a product return material authorization number (RMA#), request technical support, or submit ideas or suggestions.
Use of Personal Information
We use your personal information for the following primary purposes:
to make the Site easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than once;
to respond to your literature requests, RMA# requests, and technical support requests;
to evaluate and respond to your ideas or suggestions; and
to analyze your use of the Site and purchases of our products to make our marketing efforts more effective and improve our product offerings to you.
From time to time, we may also alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new services from Sciencetech, unless you request otherwise.
Unless otherwise stated on the Site, Sciencetech will not share your personal information with other companies. Sciencetech will disclose your personal information only in special cases, such as (i) to comply with valid legal requirements, such as a law, regulation, search warrant, subpoena or court order; or (ii) when Sciencetech has reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who, intentionally or unintentionally, may be causing injury or harm to Sciencetech-inc.com users or other persons or violating the Terms and Conditions of Use for this Site.
In the event that Sciencetech, or any component of Sciencetech's operations, is merged with, or is acquired by, another entity, then any such successor or acquiring entity may become the successor to our obligations with respect to the personal information that you have provided to Sciencetech, which would be necessary for the entity to effectively continue Sciencetech's business. By using this Site, you consent to any such use of your personal information by such an entity assuming control of Sciencetech's operations as a result of a merger, purchase of Sciencetech assets, or liquidation of Sciencetech in bankruptcy or insolvency.
You can use most of the Site without providing personal information; however, you will need to provide personal information in order to request literature or technical support, obtain an RMA#, or see product price and availability information.
If you do not want Sciencetech to communicate with you about other offers regarding Sciencetech products, programs, events, or services by e-mail, postal mail, or telephone, you may select the option when prompted stating that you do not wish to receive marketing messages from Sciencetech.
Non-Personally Identifiable Information
Internet Protocol (IP) Address
Every computer on the Internet is identified by a unique number called an Internet Protocol (IP) address. Each time you connect to the Internet, your machine is assigned an IP address. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with the Site, more efficiently administer the Site and better tailor our Site to your needs, and analyze trends by gathering broad demographic information.
Cookies
When you enter the Site, we create your profile, assign a personal identification number, then send this personal identification number back to your hard drive in the form of a cookie, which is a very small bit of code (a few kilobytes) that contains no personal information. This code is uniquely yours and allows you to navigate the Site without having to fill out registration forms with information you have already provided as long as you are using the same computer from which you initially supplied the information. Two other cookies may also be written to your hard disk at various times you are navigating our Site that allow us to remember what is in your on-line quotation and provide you with the proper pricing for your location. Additionally, if you are interrupted before finalizing an on-line quotation request, your order contents may be preserved for up to two weeks. Should you delete these cookies from your computer, you would simply have to provide your contact information again where a form is presented and you would lose the contents of your quotation. Should you decide to set your browser to reject cookies, you can still browse the Site, but on-line quotation generation and item prices may not be available.
We do not engage in list selling or "cookie swapping" with other companies.
Links
This Site contains hyperlinks to other sites. Sciencetech is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites, including any sites that may indicate a special relationship or partnership with Sciencetech. The linked sites may collect personal information from you when you link to the site. This collecting of information is not subject to Sciencetech's control. To ensure protection of your privacy, always review the privacy policy of the sites you visit by linking from our Site.
Security
Sciencetech has taken strong measures to protect the security of your personal information and to ensure that your choices for its intended use are honored. We take precautions to protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.
Notification of Changes
This Privacy Policy may be revised over time as new features are added to the Site or as Internet security and privacy standards evolve. We will post those changes prominently so you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone. We do, however, recommend that you read this Privacy Policy each time you use the Site, in case you missed our notice of changes to the Privacy Policy.
Contacting Us
If for some reason you believe Sciencetech has not adhered to this Privacy Policy, or if you have questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact Sciencetech at:
Sciencetech Inc 1450 Global Drive London, Ontario N3N 1R3
(519) 644-0135
Information
About Sciencetech
Business Development
Partners
Privacy Policy
Careers and Opportunities
Sciencetech designs and manufactures its modular systems in Canada
Sciencetech-Inc All Rights Reserved.
